Caillou?  Yoohoo.  Where are you?
卡由   你在哪
Shhhh... Gilbert, they'll hear us.
嘘   吉伯特   他们会听见的
Ooop!
喔
I think Caillou's hiding downstairs.
我想卡油躲到楼下去了
We're getting warmer.
我们好紧张
I wonder if he's in here. I don't see him.
他在这里面吗   我没看到他
No, he's not here. Let's check another room.
是的   他没在这   我们去其他房间看看
There's only one place left where Caillou could be.
只剩下最后一个卡由可能躲藏的房间了
I think I'm getting warmer and warmer.
我觉得我越来越紧张了
Caillou forgot all about being scared of Mr.Hinkle.
卡由已经忘记了对辛克尔先生的惧意
Aha!
哈哈哈
Well, I'm glad to see you two are friends now!
我很开心你们两人现在能成为朋友
I want to play again!
我想再玩一次
I'd like that very much ,Caillou!
我也喜欢玩   卡由
And this time, I'll hide and you can seek.
这次我来躲   你来找
I like you, Mr.Hinkle!
我喜欢你   辛克尔先生
Aha!
哈哈哈